GEORGE FEIGHAN

Software Developer

@ contact@georgefeighan.co.uk in linkedin.com/in/george-feighan

Withheld online

Withheld online

% georgefeighan.co.uk

PROFILE

Software developer with nearly 2 years experience developing software using both .NET and LAMP stack technologies. Highly flexible to working within different workplace environments as well as adapting solutions to changing requirements. Experience with the full development life cycle and able to anticipate and communicate the impact using strong communication skills.

SKILL HIGHLIGHTS

- Software Development and Deployment using .NET and LAMP stacks
- Requirements Analysis and Design Input
- Impact and Performance Analysis
- Technical Design and User Documentation
- Knowledge Transfer and Training
- Software Testing and Code Reviews

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Dorset Software

August 2016 - Ongoing

- Trained for 3 months .NET framework development. Covered key skills including programming standards, software testing and writing extensible and readable code.
- Spent 7 months working for a large pharmaceutical company on a major database migration project. Worked with .NET framework technologies including C#, ASP.NET, MSSQL as well as Git in an agile development environment.
- Currently working at a major bank as a web developer for a core banking support tool. Provide valuable input on design and functionality, while developing new features across all layers of the software with an emphasis on continuous delivery. Working with LAMP stack technologies including Linux, Bash, Apache, MySQL, PHP and Python as well as SVN and Git.

Maths GCSE Tutor

Action Tutoring

m Jan 2015 - March 2015

• Prepared and delivered one to one tutoring to Maths GCSE students, resulting in their greatly improved aptitude and confidence.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C# C PHI					
CSS Linux	Windows	Bash	Git TFS	Azure	gile

INTERESTS

Computer Hardware

 Have built several computers for myself and others, as well as running a cryptocurrency mining setup at university.

Music

• Attained Grade 5 for both the practical piano and written theory exams.

Outdoor Activities

 Taken part in various hiking activities including as Ten Tors and D of E, in addition to kayaking and bouldering.

EDUCATION

MSci Physics with Astrophysics (2:1) The University of Bristol

M Oct 2012 - June 2016

- Worked on a number of computational projects involving analysis of large datasets
- Gained first class marks in the C programming modules
- Co-founded The Tolkien Society and acted as treasurer

A-Level Physics (A*)
A-Level Further Mathematics (A)
A-Level Mathematics (A)
AS-Level Chemistry (B)

Exeter College

Sept 2010 - June 2012

GCSEs (4 A*, 4 A, 2 B)

West Exe Technology College

Sept 2005 - June 2010

REFEREES

Available upon request